you know i really need a better alarm
system because this is the most annoying
thing in the world and all i'm trying to
do is play
some
tic-tac-toe or naughts and crosses with
my friend i mean this isn't this is
going to end in a tie right because he's
going to go there and then and then and
then i'll go there and then he'll go
here and then it'll it'll be a tie it'll
straight up be a tie all right let's
send this back bye bye
and
hello everyone and welcome back to
another episode of hermitcraft today is
the end
of the head game
is the end of the minecraft head game
and
scar and i are about to execute our plan
but first i need to tell you about the
big event that happened earlier today
in which
a lot of things happened basically
cleo started a big arena where we had to
go against bosses hello everybody
welcome to the arena she divided us into
two teams and then we fought our first
mini boss stress monster then it went
something like this
i'm so
rubbish yes yes
yes
and then as you saw
i got the kill
meaning i got an extra thousand points
for team ska group skascarians screen
me and scar
and then the other team went against
tango and that went something like this
a little bit too late
i can't get through i'm stuck
i can't move
and then we went up against ren who was
probably the worst boss out of all of
them and it went like this all right
i'ma show you the meaning of pain
unfortunately iskall got the kill just
before me on that one so
didn't didn't get that one and then
finally b-dubs was the last mini boss
and then to finish it all off we had a
giant free-for-all and then this
happened
so i only got one win but that was more
than enough but now it's time
to go and meet scar
and get started on project uh
what's it called
ah hello hello are you ready for
operation
wait what was it fire like dude
lightning i'm so glad you said that
because i didn't know what it was either
i've forgotten one though
it's time to reveal our plans to the
audience yes that's you looking looking
at us right now
you
that's you
we are going to we discovered that if
you slay a villager it has a 100
drop rate
so our plan is to get as many villagers
bred in this tiny area as possible and
then
execute order cntcs
on them
i have got all of the necessary here
we've got and here's the thing because
cleo we don't want to give like a
thousand pillager heads or a thousand
cave spider heads we have prepared all
of the different kinds of
workstations so we will supply
hundreds of different kinds of villager
heads and as far as i'm aware she has
none of those so it should not only be a
really good submission for cleo in
getting all of the minecraft heads but
also it should secure the victory for us
what do you think scott should we get
going
victory and being polite to clear by
giving her a variety that right there is
a win-win
that is the win-win go and uh let's go
and get patient zero shall we or
patience zero patient zero the the
hamburger villagers are you ready
the ocelots are sad they're like where's
our friends going i don't know what
you've got going on here with these cat
burgers but
that's kind of weird
you do what you got to do down here
we're sending these guys over to the the
breeding center let's lock them in get
started
[Music]
so
scar this is
insane
also it's bedtime
look at them all going nappy nap
oh goodness
have you seen
anything
so ridiculous in minecraft
ah it's almost like a glorious sight
seeing all the different little heads
and all the different little outfits
they look so like looking at each other
like hey are you going are you going to
sleep
i'm asleep i i am very asleep then why
are your eyes open i don't know
this guy's lost he can't find his bed
this is absolutely
nuts
i i love it and you know what the worst
oh there they go
whenever they come out of bed they're
always perfectly in mine as well oh
do you know what the worst thing is
about this
hi
the worst thing about this dude is that
this is like 300 points
only 300 points i hope cleo gives us
some like
points for effort because this this took
like four hours
i'm i'm not i'm not breeding any more of
these guys this is just enough
yeah viewers give us some pats on the
back some handshakes some high fives and
fist bumps yes please
please appreciate what we did for the
content
so now comes the unfortunate part of
this saga they're all all these beds are
occupied
i think it's it's time to um
release
or relieve these uh villages of their
their heads
dude you're popular
you can't find me
you can't touch this
i can't touch this
time to blend in
you've got like a weird color oh that is
so funny you know i i kind of feel bad
about doing this but it's got to be done
it is time to execute order 66.
what about the younglings
even the younglings
[Music]
wow
how do you feel
great actually a little bit relieved
honestly right let's get a head count
dude
literally head count what we got dude we
got no points from this this was such a
waste of time
been digging this this operation up
oh that's just embarrassing
i hope i think cleo will appreciate the
effort ah wasn't it nice to feel the
rage flow through us
feel anger and to take that into account
i mainly feel like we wasted a lot of
time but it was fun here we've got
the secret weapon the villagers might
have been a bit of a letdown but we've
got some last minute bounties and we've
got the 56 dragon heads i would say
all together we've got an extra
one to two thousand points i'm not
entirely sure
do you think cleo should throw in
another prize for us not just the
diamonds honestly i i think the the
diamonds are fine it's just i hope she
gives us more points for these uh
villager heads because there there's
someone else there that's a that's a
prize that is a prize look at all that
what an insane amount
of of submission that is
man
whether we win or lose we are done with
the with the head game now so
it's been a good time i've never worked
harder in minecraft in my life in my
life me either i've never been to
bounties murder
i don't regret a thing
you don't you don't regret going to the
dark side briefly no i really i really
harnessed it for a while it felt good
but i put it aside because i know the
path that it could take me down goodbye
goodbye green
goodbye
there's very little we can do about the
head games now it's all submitted so we
can turn our attention back to the
glorious floating mansion and actually
that's something that i wanted to work
on a little bit today i've been messing
around in my creative world trying to
figure out how to put buildings here
and it's not easy it's not easy because
obviously this is on a solid platform
and hopefully we should get some terrain
around here so that's kind of what i
wanted to work on i thought maybe
these arches could extend quite a way
down and i could have like a little
waterfall that came out here and then
that would mean i could have a building
there now we are going to work on this
but unfortunately i need more terracotta
and terracotta is not something that's
kind of easy to buy i can get a little
bit from my trading villages but not
enough so it's much faster if i just go
and collect some
oh hold the phone there is a message
here
monsters brew new shop opening soon
please read gorgeous hermit i will be
opening a brand new shop very soon over
in the shopping district and i need your
help i call on you to help me decide
what potions should be sold can you
write the three potions you would buy
and then your name after signing return
this to the great willow tree
over at the shopping district then once
it's returned can you press the button
by the quadrant to win some diamonds yay
invisibility i would definitely buy fire
resistance
and i would definitely buy
slow falling there we go top three done
oh i need to sign it well we can deliver
this and see if we win some diamonds
that would be cool
now where am i looking for this thing
willow tree aha that looks like the
ticket
please put return books in here press
for reward i i hear i hear something
two diamonds nice
just for signing a book
amazing
and while we're here
i would love to have a little go at this
i never got it a chance
this is isko's treasure island pay one
diamond block to mine a shulker box some
gems have treasure some don't you get to
keep the gem and the contents do you get
to keep the shulker box oh yeah you do
you do you get to keep it so how do i
pay ah okay there you go diamond block
let's hope we get something good here
this one
red shulker box
ah
nothing
nothing what an expensive shulker box
that was come on i gotta win at least
something a cup a stack of stone or
something
all right all right all right all right
uh let's go for this one here and
uh a puff of fish called kenny you know
what i'm done with this game i just
wasted a load of diamonds on this using
up most of my funds stupid game and
let's take a look at the barge while
we're here again again sold loads and
loads of gravel
wow look at that okay i got all my money
back that i just wasted and sand yes i
can't believe we got to restock again so
last episode i asked should we keep the
barge and make something new and oh my
goodness the amount of people that are
badge budge
badge that's what you guys sound like by
the way you want to keep the barge okay
so i i have to think about what i'm
gonna do here then i have an idea i can
actually expand this even more and maybe
create like another layer on the barge
but i'm not entirely sure i could just
leave it as it is but it is not great
for storing stuff like i've only got a
few barrels of stuff oh what about the
the carrots look at that this is the
stonks this is the stonk sparrow right
here okay that's all our reinvestment
stuff
so i'm thinking i'm thinking that i i i
properly go for the for the barge more
and more and more make it bigger and
bigger and bigger and then later on
we'll make a different shot because yeah
it turns out you guys don't want me to
get rid of it so we're not going to but
what we are going to do is keep working
on the base now i did say earlier i need
to go and get some terracotta and that's
what we're going to go and do now
now that we've got our terracotta it's
time to start working on this little
section right here
i'm thinking i'm just gonna go for it
i've got an idea in my head this is very
dangerous i'm gonna do a little bit of
terraining just basic terraining no
details but hopefully we can get some of
the shape and everything else
the problem i'm having with this base
right is that i keep working on the
front and just completely ignoring the
back and i think
that is what i'm going to do until the
actual front and i mean all of it down
to the the gardens and the details
everything the terraining because i want
to define all the bits of the style
first just before we get
going on absolutely everything it's been
a long time since i built anything quite
like this maybe years and years ago
oh hey mumbo said hey gee are you in
your base yeah gotta i've got a message
for you oh is he sending is he sending
me he's sending me mail
mumbo's sending me something in the mail
oh it's not here all right i guess now
i'm now i'm now i'm waiting by the post
box for this message to arrive what has
my life become now i don't know what to
do he said he's sending me something in
the mail
do i do i just
do i just talk about the base more and
then come back
i need to know what he said he hasn't
even sent back his notes and crosses oh
no there it is there it is there it is
[Music]
a mess
he sent himself
[Music]
well this is a nice surprise hi mumbo
hello
[Laughter]
a message huh
yeah i mean yeah i mean it's
it's uh an important
message it's an important message that i
felt like
uh yeah there was only really one way
that i could request it or send it and i
thought you know a piece of paper
wouldn't quite do
i have i have something to tell you dude
what
uh you
i'm moving out my hobbit hole okay
uh i'm gonna keep i'm gonna keep on top
of your messages don't don't get me
wrong okay we're gonna keep those
flowing okay
you're moving out
you're moving away
i'm i'm moving 15 50 blocks away exactly
okay i'm not exactly okay
okay but
this outfit has to go dude i i i i don't
think i can be a hobbit anymore you know
you're i mean you're going to be the
only hog i i
i'm moving to my mansion and i gave up
being a hobbit a long time ago so i've
been the only hobbit yeah
you've been the only hobby for a while
i've been a solo hobbit i was only
staying a hobby because i thought you're
all of it but i didn't even realize that
you would stop being of it well this is
awful okay well dude quickly okay
bone mail me and stop me from being a
hobbit please
it's the unhobbit of bone meal how does
this work do i just write i think you
just right click me yeah all right you
ready
yep three
two one
uh boom you're back
am i back has it worked
has that actually worked
i've picked it up again i wonder what
happens if i do it again no no no no no
no no no no no no
no no no
let's throw that in the corner and never
speak of it again well uh it's been fun
i'm i was going to do like a sad speech
about how you're now the only solo
hobbit but now i found out that i was
the last hobbit and i was just kind of
hanging on to that thing how
embarrassing i'm going to send myself
back thank you very much i do appreciate
you de-hobbiting me though that's
okay that was super weird
um but i think it's time to do the thing
let's start the time lapse oh that was a
that was like a triple barrel roll all
right let's go uh unfortunately
very unfortunately
the footage for the time lapse
corrupted i got a an error
and it just it just poof doesn't exist
instead here is a montage of me being
very sad
[Music]
however
i have completed this section that i was
wondering how to tackle and good times
with scar actually helped me a little
bit with some terraining we did this
together and we've got what i think is a
really really nice feature
underneath here we've got a waterfall
that fills up this part and makes its
way through
and falls over the edge
but check it out there's no details on
this yet but it gives a really nice
perception of depth to this build and
i'm really really happy with how this
has come out look you can see down there
but you can't quite see the bottom it's
i don't know it's i think this is uh a
nice stroke of
inspiration and
last minute ideas that this has come
from and i'm really happy because this
is quite a tight squeeze through here so
i'm gonna need some opinions on this i
think that this is actually looking
pretty good but it's quite bold here i
might move this part of the build down a
couple of blocks to make it all fit a
bit nicer i think this is a a spot too
tall but i mean that's moving something
down
a couple of blocks is probably the worst
thing you got to do as a minecraft
builder okay because like imagine if i
messed up this entire build by one block
and i had to move everything
every single thing you might as well
just tear it down and start all over
again fortunately this is not a big deal
it's just a little bit too tall on one
section i think this bit is fine and i
think this bit's fine but overall i'm
pretty happy with it and you can also
see
this this uh gradient that i've been
using now it looks really really obvious
here you can see the grey world and the
grey concrete however i have actually
done this gradient thing on the entire
build you can see look gray wool powder
cyan terracotta and you don't notice
when you look at it from afar so once
this is all detailed you will barely be
able to notice but unfortunately that is
all we have time for today so i want to
say a huge thank you for watching a huge
thank you to cleo for a fantastic game
that we did we've now cleared up all of
the uh the the uh area that we uh
yeah well you know what let's just never
speak about this ever again you know
the dark side and all that thank you
very much for watching and good
bye